{
  "easy": [
    {
      "question": "Which company developed Dead by Daylight?",
      "options": ["Valve", "Behavior Interactive", "Rockstar Games", "EA"],
      "correctAnswer": "Behavior Interactive"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary objective of the Survivors in Dead by Daylight?",
      "options": [
        "Eliminate all Killers",
        "Repair generators and escape",
        "Defeat other survivors",
        "Collect bloodpoints"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Repair generators and escape"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a Killer in Dead by Daylight?",
      "options": ["Dwight", "Meg", "The Nurse", "Kate"],
      "correctAnswer": "The Nurse"
    }
  ],
  "medium": [
    {
      "question": "Which perk allows a Survivor to see the Killer’s aura when they are healing?",
      "options": [
        "Dead Hard",
        "Borrowed Time",
        "Object of Obsession",
        "Iron Will"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Object of Obsession"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the Killer who has a special ability called 'The Hunt'?",
      "options": ["The Hillbilly", "The Trapper", "The Cannibal", "The Pig"],
      "correctAnswer": "The Pig"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a map in Dead by Daylight?",
      "options": [
        "Autohaven Wreckers",
        "The Gloomy Swamp",
        "Red Forest",
        "Coldwind Farm"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "The Gloomy Swamp"
    }
  ],
  "hard": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the entity that governs the rituals in Dead by Daylight?",
      "options": ["The Dark One", "The Entity", "The Overseer", "The Hunter"],
      "correctAnswer": "The Entity"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Killer’s special ability involves placing bear traps on the map?",
      "options": [
        "The Plague",
        "The Trapper",
        "The Ghost Face",
        "The Deathslinger"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "The Trapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which map was introduced with the 'All-Kill' chapter?",
      "options": [
        "The Coldwind Farm",
        "The Raccoon City Police Department",
        "The Midwich Elementary School",
        "The Yamaoka Estate"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "The Raccoon City Police Department"
    }
  ],
  "bonus": [
    {
      "question": "Which Survivor is known for their obsession with photography and has the perk 'Lithe'?",
      "options": ["Kate Denson", "Meg Thomas", "Laurie Strode", "Nia Carlson"],
      "correctAnswer": "Nia Carlson"
    },
    {
      "question": "What creator created the TikTok sound, 'Take A Hit Makeala, Take A Hit!'?",
      "options": ["Mish, Sainty, Cam Loso, Zerbs"],
      "correctAnswer": "Mish"
    },
    {
      "question": "Blah Blah Blah",
      "options": [""],
      "correctAnswer": ""
    }
  ]
}
